Get in touch



Summary

New York based UX Designer accepting challenging new projects. My experience with product design spans across research, strategy, interaction design, visual design, testing, and development.

Recent Projects

Blocbox is a responsive website that allows users to collect and store data in a single platform. Working in Balsamiq, Sketch, HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

FoodTrux is an iOS mobile app prototype designed to simplify the food truck payments process. Working in Sketch, AdobeCS.

Seabikes is an e-commerce mobile app prototype designed to increase conversion rates for purchases of water bikes. Working in Sketch & Axure.

Education

Saint Joseph's University - Erivan K. Haub School of Business

B.S. Business Administration

Bloc.io

UX/UI Design Apprenticeship

University of Virginia - Darden School of Business Agile Development Specialization (currently in progress)

Experience

UX/UI Design Apprenticeship (Mar 2017- Oct 2018)

Bloc.io

- Completed 750+ hour project-based UX Design work under the mentorship of 2 accomplished UX professionals.
- Developed user surveys and conducted interviews for creation of personas, user stories, user requirements, and user flows.
- Created brand identities such as brand name, logo, typography, layout, color palette, and style guide.
- Built prototypes and iterated based on user testing. Prototypes included clickable lo-fi & hi-fi wireframes, as well as html/css/javascript for mobile and responsive web applications.

Manager Business Development (Dec 2017- Current)

Synechron

- Responsible for creation and management of the sales process, account-based marketing, client relationship management, and overall engagement strategy for the Morgan Stanley account.
- Develop strategic partnerships aimed at the adoption of innovative technology solutions and project-based consulting engagements.
- Collaborate with design team to proactively build prototypes of AI/ML solutions aimed at solving various business use case problems, and presented solutions to executive teams at Morgan Stanley, communicating the overall benefits to the business and cost savings.
- Successfully grew our digital (UX/UI design), technology, and business consulting practices within Morgan
 Stanley by working with our global team to increase the headcount from 250 to 350+ consultants in 12 months.

Technology Sales Executive (Jan 2013- Dec 2017)

PCM, FusionStorm

- Provided a consultative approach when recommending and designing end to end technology solutions for cloud, on-premise, and hybrid data center solutions.
- Presented solutions to customer executive teams (IT Directors, CIO's, COO's CFO's, etc) explaining the benefits, overall transformation strategy, and return on investment.
- Worked closely with district managers, inside sales representatives, engineering team, legal team, and project managers to ensure open communication and a successful delivery of the contracted solutions.
- Oversaw entire project lifecycle and ensured recommended solutions met all required business, technical, and financial objectives.

Skills

Visual Design
UX/UI Design
Project Management
User Research & Testing
Brand Strategy & Identity
Information Architecture
Personas & UserStories
Wireframing & Prototyping

<u>Tools</u>

Sketch3
Axure RP Pro
Balsamiq
Adobe CS
InVision
Atom
Git/GitHub
HTML5, CSS3
& JavaScript